{
    "subject": "resource/101_Dalmatians_II:_Patch's_London_Adventure",
    "predicate": "property/music",
    "object": "resource/Richard_Gibbs",
    "human_readable": "The music for '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure' was composed by Richard Gibbs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869726300239563,
            "question": "Who composed the music for '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9572495222091675,
            "question": "What kind of work did Richard Gibbs do on '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9459078907966614,
            "question": "What is the genre of '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7828664183616638,
            "question": "What year was '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7710726857185364,
            "question": "Who directed '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7687572240829468,
            "question": "What is the name of the film for which Richard Gibbs composed music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7396525144577026,
            "question": "Is Richard Gibbs a composer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7360798120498657,
            "question": "What other types of music has Richard Gibbs composed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7259505391120911,
            "question": "Can you name another film for which Richard Gibbs composed music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7235755324363708,
            "question": "Is Richard Gibbs known for composing music for animated films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The music for '101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure' was composed by Richard Gibbs.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7850_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film for which Richard Gibbs composed music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7850_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other types of music has Richard Gibbs composed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7850_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Richard Gibbs a composer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7850_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7850_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents confirm that the music score for \"101 Dalmatians II: Patch's London Adventure\" was indeed composed by Richard Gibbs."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}